Guide to the Arden B. Schell Watergate Collection, 1972-1974
George Mason University Libraries
- Arden B. Schell Watergate collection, 1972-1974
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    2.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.4), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    2.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (7.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    2.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    2.70
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    2.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.4), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    2.72
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    2.73
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    2.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (13.1), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    2.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.3), 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    2.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    2.77 (Executive clemency; Camp David, Maryland; San Clemente, California) Bank of America; James Bierbower; Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Sam Ervin (US Senate); Fred Fielding; Patrick Gray (nomination); H.R. Haldeman; Lawrence Higby; Thomas Hogan; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Paul O'Brien; Paul O'Connor; Henry Peterson; Robert Reisner; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; Charles Shaffer; Gordon Strachan; Washington Post; Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (15.1 - 15.5), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    2.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (16.1 - 16.8), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    2.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (17.1 - 17.7), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    2.80
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (18.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    2.81
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (19.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    2.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.6), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    2.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    2.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.9), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    2.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (23.1 - 23.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    2.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (24.1 - 24.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    2.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (25.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    2.88
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (26.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    2.89
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (27.1 - 27.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    2.90
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (28.1 - 28.4), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    2.91
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    2.92
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (30.1 - 30.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    2.93
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    2.94
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (32.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    2.95
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 2 (33.1 - 33.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    2.96
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    2.97 ("Gemstone" Operation; Key Biscayne, Florida; Las Vegas, Nevada); Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean; Democratic National Committee (DNC); John Ehrlichman; Fountainbleau Hotel; Hank Greenspun; H.R. Haldeman; Thomas Hart; Lawrence Higby; Howard E. Hunt; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Robert Mardian; James McCord; George McGovern; John N. Mitchell; Henry Peterson; Herbert Porter; Earl Silbert; Gordon Strachan; Watergate Hotel
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (34.1 - 34.7), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    2.98
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (35.1 - 35.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    2.99
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (36.1 - 36.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    3.1
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (37.1 - 37.5), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    3.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (38.1 - 38.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    3.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (39.1 - 39.5), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    3.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (40.1), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    3.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (41.1 - 41.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    3.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (42.1 - 42.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    3.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (43.1 - 43.3), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    3.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (44.1 - 44.5), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    3.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    3.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (46.1 - 46.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    3.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (47.1 - 47.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    3.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (48.1 - 48.2), 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    3.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 3 (49.1 - 49.5), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    3.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    3.15 (Executive privilege; "Gemstone" Operation); Charles Colson; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP) (payment of Watergate defendants); John Dean (Obstruction of justice; Resignation; Testimony); John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Lewis Fielding; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; Thomas Hart; Lawrence Higby; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Jeb Stuart Magruder; John N. Mitchell; Jacki Nesbitt; Henry Peterson; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; Gordon Strachan; Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (50.1 - 50.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    3.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (51.1 - 51.6), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    3.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (52.1 - 52.4), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    3.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (53.1 - 53.4), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    3.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (53.5 - 53.10), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    3.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (54.1 - 54.4), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    3.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (55.1 - 55.8), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    3.22
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (56.1 - 56.5), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    3.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (56.6 - 56.8), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    3.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (57.1 - 57.7), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    3.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (58.1 - 58.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    3.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (59.1 - 59.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    3.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (60.1 - 60.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    3.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (61.1 - 61.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    3.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (62.1 - 62), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    3.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (63.1 - 63.5), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    3.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (64.1 - 64.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    3.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 4 (65.1 - 65.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    3.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    3.34 (White House tape recordings); Stephen Bull; Dwight Chapin; Ken Clawson; John Dean (Immunity; Testimony); John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Lewis Fielding; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; J. Edgar Hoover; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Fred Larue; George Gordon Liddy; Clark MacGregor; Jeb Stuart Magruder; James McCord; John N. Mitchell; Richard Moore; Henry Peterson; Herbert Porter; William Rogers; Secret Service; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; Gordon Strachan; Frank Strickler; John Wilson; Ronald Ziegler
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (66.1 - 66.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    3.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (67.1 - 67.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    3.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (68.1 - 68.3), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    3.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (69.1 - 69.5), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    3.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (70.1 - 70.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    3.39
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (71.1 - 71.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    3.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (72.1 - 72.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    3.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (73.1 - 73.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    3.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (74.1), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    3.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (75.1 - 75.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    3.44
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (76.1 - 76.10), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    3.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (77.1 - 77.8), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    3.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (78.1 - 78.5), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    3.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (79.1 - 79.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    3.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (80.1 - 80.2), 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    3.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    3.50 (Camp David, Maryland; Key Biscayne, Florida; White House tape recordings) Stephen Bull; John Dean; John Ehrlichman; Patrick Gray; H.R. Haldeman; Lawrence Higby; Howard E. Hunt; Herbert Kalmbach; Richard Kleindienst; Jeb Stuart Magruder; Henry Peterson; Elliot Richardson; Senate Select Committee on Presidential Campaign Activities; Washington Post; Lowell Weicker (US Senate); Ronald Ziegler; Raymond Zumwalt
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (81.1 - 81.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    3.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (82.1 - 82.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    3.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (83.1 - 83.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    3.53
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (84.1 - 84.9), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    3.54
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (85.1 - 85.6), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    3.55
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (86.1), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    3.56
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (87.1 - 87.6), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    3.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (88.1 - 88.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    3.58
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (89.1 - 89.3), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    3.59
  - Evidentiary Notebook 4, Vol. 5 (90.1), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    3.60
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    3.61 (Revenue sharing); Spiro Agnew; Dita Beard; Canteen Corporation; Casey Thomas; Dwight Chapin; John Ehrlichman; Peter Flanigan; Harold S. Geneen; Edward Gerrity; Grinnel Corporation; Erwin Griswold; Hartford Fire Insurance Company; House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee; James (General) Hughes; Tod Hullin; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Richard Kleindienst; Richard McLaren; William Merriam; John N. Mitchell; Michael Mitchell; Office of Foreign Direct Investment; Peter Peterson; John Poole; Felix Rohatyn; John Ryan; George Schultz; Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC); Hugh Sloan; Maurice Stans; Lawrence Walsh
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.6), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    3.62
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.4), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    3.63
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.4), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    3.64
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (4.1), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    3.65
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.12), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    3.66
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.3), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    3.67
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    3.68
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.3), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    3.69
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (9.1), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    3.70
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    3.71
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    3.72
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.5), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    3.73
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (13.1 - 13.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    3.74
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    3.75
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (15.1 - 15.5), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    3.76
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (16.1 - 16.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    3.77
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (17.1 - 17.2), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    3.78
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 1 (18.1), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    3.79
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    3.80 (1972 Republican National Convention; San Diego, California; Sheraton Harbor Island Hotel); Jack Anderson; Dita Beard; Canteen Corporation; Chicago Tribune; John Connally; Committee to Re-elect the President (CRP); Robert Dole; John Ehrlichman; Peter Flanigan; Harold S. Geneen; Jo Good; Grinnel Corporation; H.R. Haldeman; Hartford Fire Insurance Company; Lawrence Higby; Brit Hume; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Howard James (President, ITT-Sheraton); Herbert Klein; Richard Kleindienst; Egil Krogh; Jeb Stuart Magruder Paul McCracken; Richard McLaren; William Merriam; John N. Mitchell; Michael Mitchell; Louis Nunn; Robert Odle; Peter Peterson; Richard Ramsden; Ed Reinecke (Lt. Governor, California); Republican National Committee; Felix Rohatyn; Senate Committee on the Judiciary; Gordon Strachan; William Timmons; Washington Post; Bob Wilson (US Representative)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (19.1 - 19.4), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    3.81
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.4), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    3.82
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.5), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    3.83
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.13), 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    3.84
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (23.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    3.85
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (24.1 - 24.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    3.86
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (25.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    3.87
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (26.1 - 26.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    3.88
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (27.1 - 27.4), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    3.89
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (28.1 - 28.11), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    3.90
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.3), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    3.91
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (30.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    3.92
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (31.1 - 31.4), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    3.93
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (32.1 - 32.6), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    3.94
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (33.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    3.95
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (34.1 - 34.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    3.96
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (35.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    3.97
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 2 (36.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    3.98
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    4.1 (Denver, Colorado; Key Biscayne, Florida) Birch Bayh (US Senate); Dita Beard; William Casey; Charles Colson; John Connally; John Dean; James O. Estland (US Senate); John Ehrlichman; Ralph Erickson; Fred Fielding; Harold S. Geneen; Edward Gerrity; Grinnel Corporation; H.R. Haldeman; J. Edgar Hoover; House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee; Howard E. Hunt; International Telephone and Telegraph (ITT); Wallace Johnson; Edward M. Kennedy (US Senate); Herbert Klein; Richard Kleindienst; Clark MacGregor; Charles Mallory; Robert Mardian; William Merriam; John N. Mitchell; Michael Mitchell; Richard Moore; New York Times; Peter Peterson; John Ryan; Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC); Joseph Snyder, MD; Harley Staggers; William Timmons; John Tunney (US Senate); Washington Post
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (37.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    4.2
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (38.1 - 38.3), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    4.3
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (39.1 - 39.6), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    4.4
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (40.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    4.5
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (41.1 - 41.7), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    4.6
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (42.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    4.7
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (43.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    4.8
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (44.1 - 44.5), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    4.9
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (45.1 - 45.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    4.10
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (46.1 - 46.4), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    4.11
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (47.1 - 47.3), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    4.12
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (48.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    4.13
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (49.1 - 49.15), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    4.14
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (50.1 - 50.3), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    4.15
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (51.1 - 51.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    4.16
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (52.1 - 52.6), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    4.17
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (53.1 - 53.4), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    4.18
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (54.1 - 54.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    4.19
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (55.1 - 55.9), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    4.20
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (56.1 - 56.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    4.21
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (57.1), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    4.22
  - Evidentiary Notebook 5, Vol. 3 (58.1 - 58.2), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    4.23
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    4.24 (Chicago, Illinois; Milk--Price supports for) Associated Milk Producers, Inc. (AMPI); Albert Brewer; Murray Chotiner; Charles Colson; Harry Dent; John Ehrlichman; Tom Evans; Peter Flanigan; Jack Gleason; H.R. Haldeman; Marion Harrison; Patrick J. Hillings; Robert Isham; Herbert Kalmbach; Robert Lilly; Harold Nelson; Richard M. Nixon (re-election campaign); David Parr; Maurice Stans; Anthony Ulasewicz; Wagner and Baroody; George Wallace
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.6), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    4.25
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.5), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    4.26
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.6), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    4.27
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (4.1), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    4.28
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.7), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    4.29
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    4.30
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    4.31
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    4.32
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    4.33
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    4.24
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (1.1 - 1.6), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (2.1 - 2.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (3.1 - 3.6), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (4.1), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (5.1 - 5.7), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (6.1 - 6.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (7.1 - 7.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (8.1 - 8.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (9.1 - 9.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (10.1 - 10.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    4.34
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (11.1 - 11.4), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    4.35
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (12.1 - 12.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    4.36
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (13.1), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    4.37
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 1 (14.1 - 14.4), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    4.38
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    4.39 (Price supports for milk); Carl Albert; Associated Milk Producers, Inc. (AMPI); John Byrnes; Murray Chotiner; Charles Colson; John Connally; Robert Dole; John Ehrlichman; William Galbraith; H.R. Haldeman; Gary Hanman; Clifford Hardin; Marion Harrison; Lawrence Higby; Jacob Jacobsen; Herbert Kalmbach; Robert Lilly; Clark MacGregor; Wilbur Mills; Harold Nelson; Richard M. Nixon (re-election campaign); Office of Management and Budget; David Parker; Kenneth Parkinson; George Schultz; Gary Seevers; Earl Silbert; Gordon Strachan; US Department of Agriculture (USDA); Wagner and Baroody; John Whitaker
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (15.1 - 15.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    4.40
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (16.1 - 16.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    4.41
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (17.1), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    4.42
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (18.1 - 18.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    4.43
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (19.1 - 19.6), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    4.44
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (20.1 - 20.7), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    4.45
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (21.1 - 21.4), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    4.46
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (22.1 - 22.12), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    4.47
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (23.1 - 23.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    4.48
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (24.1 - 24.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    4.49
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (25.1 - 25.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    4.50
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (26.1 - 26.4), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    4.51
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (27.1), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    4.52
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (28.1 - 28.4), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    4.53
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 2 (29.1 - 29.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    4.54
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    4.55 (Chicago, Illinois; Louisville, Kentucky; "Plumbers" Unit) Associated Milk Producers, Inc. (AMPI); Robert Bennett; Phillip Campbell; Murray Chotiner; John Connally; Dairymen, Inc.; John Ehrlichman; Daniel Ellsberg; Clifford Hardin; Marion Harrison; Jacob Jacobsen; Herbert Kalmbach; Harold Nelson; Richard M. Nixon (re-election campaign); Lee Nunn; Donald Rice; George Schultz; Hugh Sloan; Gordon Strachan; Wagner and Baroody; John Whitaker
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (30.1 - 30.3), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    4.56
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (31.1 - 31.2), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    4.57
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (32.1 -32.7), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    4.58
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (33.1 - 33.5), 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    4.59
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (34.1 - 34.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    4.60
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (35.1 - 35.3), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    4.61
  - Evidentiary Notebook 6, Vol. 3 (36.1 - 36.10), 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    4.62